by RentAnAdviser.com
We took it all apart but I
am wishing I had stayed
In the back room something
I heard you say
We didn′t wanna call it too early
Now it seems a world away
but I miss that day
Are we ever gona feel the same?
Standing in the light till It
is over‚ out of our minds
Someone had to draw a line
We′ll be coming back for you one day
I don′t even care if I know
you‚ out of our minds
Sad to leave it all behind
We′ll be coming back
We′ll be coming back for you one day
You can see it from afar‚ we
were riding that wave
Blinded by the lights‚ and
It is something I crave
We didn′t want to call it too early
Now it seems a world away
but I miss that day
Are we ever gona feel the same?
Standing in the light till It
is over‚ out of our minds
Someone had to draw a line
We′ll be coming back for you one day
I don′t even care if I know
you‚ out of our minds
Sad to leave it all behind
We′ll be coming back for you one day
Gona rise‚ gona fall‚ getting
pulled apart
And we all do it all cause
it stole our hearts
Gona light up the skies‚
so ignore the stars
And we all do it all cause
it stole our hearts
Standing in the light till It
is over‚ out of our minds
Someone had to draw a line
We′ll be coming back for you one day
I don′t even care if I know
you‚ out of our minds
Sad to leave it all behind
We′ll be coming back for you one day
www.RentAnAdviser.com